http://www.monkeyoffice.co.uk/help/privacy-policy

Shop By Brand
Need A Credit Account?
Basket
Homebusiness benefitsNewsletterOffice SuppliesPaper & CardPrinter & Copier PaperGraph PaperPhoto PaperWide Format PaperView allArtist & Graphic SuppliesArtist PortfoliosCutting Mats Guillotines & TrimmersScalpels View allBooksAccident BooksAccount BooksDuplicate & Triplicate BooksNotebooksView allBox FilesBriefcases, Luggage & BagsBriefcasesLaptop CasesMessenger BagsView allCard Index & SuppliesCard Index Box Card Index CabinetRecord CardsT Card Systems View allCash, Document & Suggestion BoxesCash BoxesDocument BoxesSuggestion BoxesView allClips, Pins & FastenersFoldback Clips Paperclips Rubber BandsTreasury Tags View allCorrection ProductsCorrection FluidCorrection PensCorrection RollersCorrection TapeDesktop AccessoriesClipboards ScissorsStamps & Stamp PadsThimblettes View allDiaries & PlannersCalendarsDesk DiariesYear Planners Personal OrganisersView allDrawer Sets Education SuppliesBook Covering FilmGeometry SetsRegister BooksReward StickersView allEnvelopesBrown EnvelopesWhite EnvelopesGusset EnvelopesPadded BagsView allErgonomic AccessoriesFoot RestsLaptop RisersMonitor Stands & Arms Mouse Mats & Wrist RestsView allFilingDocument Wallets Indexes & DividersPunched PocketsRing BindersView allGlue & Sticky FixersGlue SticksLiquid GlueSpray GlueSticky Tack, Strips & PadsView allLabelsInkjet LabelsLabels on RollLaser LabelsMulti Purpose LabelsView allLegal SuppliesCounsels NotebooksDocument StrapsDouble Pocket Wallet Legal CornersLegal Wallet View allLetter Trays Lever Arch FilesMagazine FilesPadsAccount PadsMemo PadsPetty Cash PadsRefill PadsView allPostage StampsPresentation BindersRing BindersStaplers, Staples & PunchesHole Punches StaplersStaple RemoversView allSticky Notes & FlagsYellow Sticky NotesColoured Sticky NotesPost-it Index TabsSticky Note DispensersStorage BoxesArchival Storage BoxesPlastic Storage BoxesStorage BinsStorage CratesTags & TicketsCloakroom TicketsStrung TagsTicket RollsUnstrung TagsTapesClear Tape Double Sided Tape Parcel TapeTape DispensersView allWriting InstrumentsBall Point PensHighlightersPermanent MarkersWhiteboard MarkersView all
Ink & TonerTechnology3D PensActivity TrackersView allBatteriesBatteriesRechargable BatteriesBattery ChargersCables & Cable ManagementCable ManagersDesk TrunkingDisplay PortsFloor CoversUSB PortsView allComputer AccessoriesDocking StationsEquipment Security Screen FiltersSpeakers WebcamsView allRobotic BallsView allComputer CleaningAir DustersComputer CleanerComputer Cleaning ClothsScreen CleanerView allDash CamsView allData MediaCard ReadersCD ReWritableData Tapes & CartridgesDVDSDHC Memory CardsUSB Flash Drives & Memory SticksView allDigital CamerasErgonomic AccessoriesCopyholders Foot RestsLaptop RisersMonitor Stands & Arms Mouse Mats & Wrist RestsView allHeadsetsInput DevicesKeyboardsMiceLabel Printers & LabelsLabel PrintersLabel Printer AdaptorsLabelling TapesLabels for Labelling MachinesLaptopsView allMonitors & TelevisionsHD TelevisionsMonitorsTV & DVD Combi'sNetworkingModems & RoutersCable ManagementDevice CablesAdaptersPrinters & Scanners3D PrintersDot Matrix PrintersFax MachinesInkjet PrintersLaser PrintersScannersView allSat NavsView allTablet & Mobile AccessoriesTabletsTablet CasesTablet Stands & KeyboardsMobile AccessoriesEarphones & HeadphonesSpeakersView allTouchscreensView allTelephones & Audio ConferencingAudio Conferencing TelephonesTelephone CleaningTwo Way RadiosVisualisersView allVR GogglesView allMachinesAir PurifiersBindingComb Binding MachinesBinding CombsBinding CoversThermal Binding CoversWire Binding MachinesBinding WiresSlide BindersView allCalculatorsDesktop CalculatorsFinancial CalculatorsPocket CalculatorsPrinting CalculatorsScientific CalculatorsCalculator AdaptorsCalculator RollsInk RollersView allDictationDictation MachinesDictation AccessoriesFansHeatersHumidity AbsorbersView allLaminatingLaminating MachinesLaminating PouchesLaminating Clips & LanyardsLaminating RollsSelfseal Laminating PouchesView allShreddingShredder Oil BottlesShredder Oil SheetsWaste SacksThermometersView allFurnitureChairs & SeatingExecutive ChairsOperator ChairsPosture ChairsStacking ChairsVisitor ChairsView allCupboardsMetal CupboardsWooden CupboardsCupboard AccessoriesSide Opening TambourView allDesksBench System DeskingRadial DesksReception DesksRectangular DesksSit Stand DesksWave DesksView allEducational FurnitureClassroom TablesExam DesksMobile Storage UnitsStacking ChairsSwivel ChairsView allFiling CabinetsHome FilersMetal Filing CabinetsWooden Filing CabinetsLockersStandard LockersClean & Dirty LockersCompartment LockersCube LockersTwin LockersUniform LockersMailroom FurnitureSorter & Pigeon Hole UnitsSorting DesksStorage UnitsMulti Drawer CabinetsMulti Drawer CabinetsInsert TraysPedestals & Side FilersDesk High PedestalsFixed PedestalsMobile PedestalsPedestal AccessoriesSide FilersScreensDesktop ScreensFloor Standing ScreensScreen AccessoriesScreen Feet & BracketsSit Stand FurnitureTablesBoardroom TablesFolding TablesFolding Table StorageMeeting TablesReception TablesWorkstationsFixed WorkstationsMobile WorkstationsMobile Printer StandsBack SupportsBistro & Breakout FurnitureBookcasesClocksDesk ClocksWall ClocksCoat Stands & Coat HooksCoat HooksCoat StandsHazardous Substance Storage CabinetsLightingDesk LampsLight Bulbs, Lamps & TubesUplightersMatsChair MatsFloor MatsOffice TrolleysOutdoor SeatingOutdoor StorageRackingRope Barrier Systems Shelf UnitsWorkbenchesPresentationBadges & AccessoriesBadge ClipsBadge Necklaces & LanyardsBadge PrintersName BadgesSecurity Pass HoldersView allBoardsCork BoardsDisplay BoardsMobile Boards & PresentersNotice BoardsWhiteboards Non-MagneticView allBoard AccessoriesBoard CleanerBoard ErasersGridding TapeMagnetsStarter KitsView allConference Folders Display BooksDisplay SystemsFlipcharts & AccessoriesDigital Flipcharts & AccessoriesFlipchart EaselsFlipchart PadsMagic ChartsTabletop ChartsView allFramesDuraframe Magnetic FramesPicture & Certificate FramesFrame HangingLiterature HoldersBusiness Card HoldersLiterature Display StandsLiterature HoldersMenu HoldersSign HoldersView allMaps Presentation EquipmentLaser PointersOHP Inkjet Transparency FilmOHP Laser Transparency FilmProjection ScreensProjectorsTouchscreensView allPresentation Portfolios FacilitiesClinical SuppliesView allHousehold SuppliesBeddingShower AccessoriesTowelsLiving RoomOutdoor LivingView allBins & Bin BagsAshtrays & Ash BinsRecycling BinsRubbish BagsRecycling SignsSwing Bin & Pedal Bin LinersWaste BinsView allCleaning EquipmentClothsDustpan & BrushesMops, Buckets & WringersScouring PadsSpongesSweepersVacuumsView allCleaning ProductsAir FreshenersBleachCar CleaningDisinfectantsMulti Purpose CleanerPolishUpholstery CleanerView allFirst AidFirst Aid Kits BandagesDefibrillatorsDressingsEye WashPlasters & Wipes View allFleet ManagementDash CamsSat NavsTachographView allHand HygieneDispensersHand CreamSanitisersSoapView allLadders & StepsLaddersLadder TagsStep StoolsMailroom & WarehouseKnives Mailroom Wallets & SealsPostal ScalesRackingTrucks & TrolleysView allPackagingBubble Film BagsBubble WrapDocuments Enclosed EnvelopesKraft Wrapping Paper Postal TubesView allProtective Clothing & EquipmentCoverallsFace MasksOvershoesSafety Goggles & SpectaclesSafety Shoes & BootsView allRetail & Point of SaleBank Note CheckersCash Registers & AccessoriesCredit Card & Cash Register Rolls EPOS SystemsLabelling & TaggingMoney CountersView allSignsCleaning SignsHealth & Safety PostersNo Smoking SignsPhotoluminescent Signs & TapeSafety SignsView allSafety & Security EquipmentCCTV & Security CamerasFire ExtinguishersKey CabinetsKey Tabs & ReelsPersonal AlarmsSafesSafety Log BooksView allToilet Rolls & Paper TowelsCentre Feed RollsFacial TissuesHand TowelsHygiene RollsToilet Rolls & DispensersView allTraffic ManagementBarrier TapesBarriersDrive Over Cable CoversKerb RampsTachographTally CountersView allWashroom EquipmentBathroom ScalesSanitary Bins & BagsToilet Brush SetsToilet Roll HoldersToilet SeatsWinter SuppliesGrit Bins & SaltSalt SpreadersSand BagsSnow ShovelsWinter KitsView allCateringAppliancesAir FryersCoffee MakersCooking HobsDishwashersFreezersDigital ThermometersFridgesKettlesMicrowavesToastersSlow CookersUrnsWashing MachinesWater DispensersView allBiscuits & SnacksBiscuitsCerealsCrispsMintsSweetsCatering SuppliesBaking Trays & DishesCake CasesCatering FoilCoffee Machine CleanerCling FilmCatering StationsCup HoldersFood StorageGreaseproof PaperPump Pots & CafetiereJugsKitchen RollKitchen ScalesNapkinsOven GlovesPots & PansSauce PortionsStrawsTable ClothsTakeaway Containers Tea TowelsTraysUtensilsView allCondimentsJamSalt & PepperSauce PortionsCups, Plates & CutleryBowlsCupsCutleryGlassesPlatesDinner SetsDrinksCoffeeFizzy DrinksHot ChocolateJuicesMilkSugarTeaWaterView allParty SuppliesBirthday BadgesBalloonsGift BagsGift WrapGamesGreenEco Friendly Art & Graphic SuppliesCutting MatsDrawing BoardsGuillotines & TrimmersMaths SetsView allEco Friendly Books & PadsAccount Books & PadsNotebooksRefill PadsShorthand PadsTelephone Address BooksView allEco Friendly Cash & Document BoxesCard Index CabinetsCash BoxesCash DrawersEco Friendly CateringCoffeeCups, Plates & CutleryFizzy DrinksNapkinsWaterView allEco Friendly Desktop AccessoriesPaperclipsRulersScissorsStamps & Stamp PadsStaplersView allEco Friendly Diaries & PlannersYear PlannersEco Friendly Envelopes & PackagingBrown EnvelopesBubble WrapKraft Wrapping PaperProtective EnvelopesWhite EnvelopesView allEco Friendly Facilities SuppliesBins & Bin BagsCleaning ProductsFirst AidToilet Rolls & Paper TowelsHealth & Safety PostersView allEco Friendly FilingCard Index FilesDocument WalletsIndexes & DividersLever Arch FilesPunched PocketsRotary Card FilesSquare Cut FoldersView allEco Friendly FurnitureChairs & SeatingCupboardsFiling CabinetsTablesWorkstationsView allEco Friendly Glue & Sticky TapesClear TapeGlue SticksParcel TapeSticky Tack, Strips & PadsTape DispensersView allEco Friendly Ink & TonerBrother Inkjet CartridgesBrother Laser DrumsBrother Laser Toner CartridgesCanon Fax CartridgesCanon Inkjet CartridgesView allEco Friendly Labels, Tags & TicketsCloakroom TicketsLaser LabelsSpine LabelsStrung TagsUnstrung TagsEco Friendly Legal SuppliesCounsels NotebooksDouble Pocket WalletsLegal CornersLegal WalletsProbate WalletsEco Friendly Office Machines & AccessoriesBinding CombsCalculator RollsDesktop CalculatorsLaminating PouchesShreddersView allEco Friendly Paper & CardBusiness FormsCardPoster PaperPrinter & Copier PaperTelex RollsView allEco Friendly Presentation & ConferenceConference Folders Display BooksLiterature HoldersFlipchart PadsWhiteboards MagneticView allEco Friendly Sticky Notes & FlagsColoured Sticky NotesYellow Sticky NotesEco Friendly TechnologyBatteriesComputer CleaningLabel Printers & LabelsMouse Mats & Wrist RestsPrinters & ScannersView allEco Friendly Writing InstrumentsBall Point PensHighlightersPencilsPermanent MarkersRollerball PensView allShopsCoffee ShopTea ShopShredder ShopSocial DistancingSignageWall SignsSite Safety SignsPostersEntrance SignsPolicy SignsBannersPost SleevesShop SignsFloor GraphicsTemporary SignsA-BoardsHygiene SignsDesktop SignsView allScreensCashier & Counter ScreensDesktop ScreensModular Desk Divider ScreensRoom Divider ScreensView allFloor Graphics & TapesFloor GraphicsFloor TapeLinemarkersView allSafety TapesBarrier TapeFloor TapesView allPPEFace MasksVisorsPlastic ApronsGlovesSpectaclesView allBody Temperature ThermometersView allHand Sanitisers & SoapView allEntrance Signs & BannersView allHygiene SignsView allShop SignsView allSite Safety SignsView allTemporary Signs & BarriersTemporary SignsBarriersA BoardsView allStencilsView allHand Towels & WipesView all
Cookie Policy
Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. By continuing to browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.
Top of Page
Help
> Privacy policy
Privacy policy
("We")
are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This
policy (together with our Terms of Website Use and any other documents referred
to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or
that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following
carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data
and how we will treat it.
For
the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), we are the data
controller.
Who will hold your information?
www.monkeyoffice.co.uk
is a site operated by Moorside Office Limited (we). We are
registered in England and Wales under company number 7112002 and with our
registered office at 1 Winnall Valley Road, Winchester,
Hampshire, SO23 0LD.
Our
VAT number is GB 983 5000 23.
Information we may collect from you
We
may collect and process the following data about you:
Personal
contact details when you register on our website or place an order for products
or services.
We
also collect information when you voluntarily fill in forms on our site
www.monkeyoffice.co.uk (our site). This includes information provided at the
time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting
material or requesting further services.
We
may ask you for information when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored
by us, and when you report a problem with our site.
We
may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP
address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to
report aggregate information to our partners. This is statistical data about
our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.
If
you complete a credit application form then we will make searches with a credit
reference agency in order to determine whether or not to grant you a credit facility.
We will make searches both in respect of your Company and its directors. We
will collect the information that you submit on the credit application form and
we will keep a copy of the search results from the credit reference agency.
Our
website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This
helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and
also allows us to improve our site. For detailed information on the cookies we
use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie policy.
Any
credit card or debit card information that you submit either through the
website or via telephone is submitted directly to a payment server of a credit
card processing company. We do not maintain electronic or physical copies of
your credit card information.
If
you communicate with us via social media, Live Chat or our feedback partner,
Feefo, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
Information
from other sources such as our retail partners, specialist companies that
provide customer information (like credit reference agencies, fraud prevention
agencies, claims databases, marking and research companies) and social media
providers as well as information that is publicly available.
Where we store your
personal data
The
data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a
destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also
be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of
our partners. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment
of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of
support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer,
storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure
that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.
Once
we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security
features appropriate to the nature of the data to try to prevent unauthorised
access. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot
guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission
is at your own risk, and we accept no liability if security is breached.
Uses made of the
information
We
use information held about you in the following ways:
To
ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for
you and for your computer.
To
carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you
and us.
To
allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you
choose to do so.
To
notify you about updates and changes to our service.
We
may use your data to contact you about products or services that may be of
interest to you. You have the right at any time to stop us contacting you for
marketing purposes. We won’t send you marketing messages if you tell us not to,
but we will still need to send you occasional service-related messages. If you
no longer wish to be contact for marketing purposes, please email
sales@monkeyoffice.co.uk or update your marketing preferences in your ‘My Account’
area on the website.
Our
site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our
partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of
these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies
and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.
Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these
websites.
We
do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our partners, but
we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we
may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement
on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help
advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women
in S11). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to
enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their
advertisement to that target audience.
Your
credit account application information will be used to help us determine whether
or not to grant you a credit facility with us and we will make searches with a
credit reference agency in order to determine whether or not to grant you a
credit facility. We will make searches both in respect of your Company and its
directors.
Disclosure of your
information
We
may disclose your personal information to third parties:
In
the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may
disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business
or assets.
If
the shares of Moorside Office Limited are acquired by a third party,
in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the
transferred assets.
If
we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply
with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms of Website Use or Terms and Conditions of Supply and other agreements; or to protect the
rights, property, or safety of us, our customers, or others. This includes
exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes
of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Access to
information
You
have the right to access the personal information that we hold about you. This
is sometimes called a “Subject Access Request”. If we agree that we are obliged
to provide personal information to you (or someone else on your behalf) we will
provide it, you or them free of charge.
Before
providing personal information to you or another person on your behalf, we may
ask for proof of identity and sufficient information about your interactions
with us that we can locate your personal information.
If
any personal information we hold is inaccurate or out of date, you may ask us
to correct it.
Right to stop or limit processing of your data
You
have the right to object to us processing your personal information if we are
not entitled to use it any more, to have your information deleted if we are
keeping it too long or have its processing restricted in certain circumstances.
If
you would like to exercise these rights, please contact us via one the
mechanisms set out below.
How long do we keep your information for?
We
will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfil the
purposes outlined in this privacy policy unless a longer retention period is
required or permitted by law.
Changes to our
privacy policy
We
keep our privacy policy under regular review. Any changes made will be posted
on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. This privacy
policy was most recently updated in May 2018.
Contact Details
If
you would like to exercise one of your rights as set out above or you have a
question or a concern about this policy or the way your personal information is
processed, please contact us by the following means:
By
Email – sales@monkeyoffice.co.uk
By
Post – Data Protection Officer, Monkey Office, 1 Winnall Valley Road, Winchester, Hampshire. SO23 0LD.
Help
Christmas and New Year Trading ArrangementsAbout usMy accountDelivery informationReturns informationContact usCall me backReduce your costsPayment informationPrice promiseFAQ'sManufacturer linksTerms and conditions of supply
Newsletter Sign Up
* Required fields are marked with an asterisk.
Please enter your details.
Sign-up with your email address to receive special offers & the latest promotions from Monkey Office
Sign Up
ORDER OR CALL US ON
0345 258 1205
Office Hours 08:30 - 17:30 Monday to Friday
